

#### PERSONAL DETAILS

• Full Name Nguyen Duc Tri

• Year of Birth 1998

• Gender Male

Citizenship Vietnamese

• Country of Residence Vietnam

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

• More than 2 years' experiences in business analyst.

• Strong problems-solving skills and in need of a challenge.

 Demonstrated ability to work independently and undertake research to find an ideal solution for a complex problem in a defined time frame.

### **EDUCATION**

• Banking Academy (08/2016 – 04/2020)

Major: Management Information System (MIS)

• Training Course at TesterHN (09/2019 – 11/2019)

Major: Manual Testing

• Training Course at FPT FIS (11/2019 – 12/2019)

Major: Deploying ERP project with SAP and Oracle tools

• Training Course at BAC (03/2022 – 03/2022)

Major: Advanced Business Analysis 3.0

#### **SKILLS**

• Design UX UI of website and app

• Collect and analyze requirement

Doing document

English

• External and internal communication

• Has knowledge about database



### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### **SPHINX JSC**

Feb 2021 - Present

Role: Business analyst

## **Responsibility:**

Involving in many projects: maintenance, ecommerce, and internal management projects,...

- Communicate, collect and analyze requirement from end client
- Design mock up of website and application
- Writing SRS document and relating document such as user guide, traceability matrix,...
- Occasionally support team as sub PM role

## FPT INFORMATION SYSTEM

Dec 2019 - Dec 2020

**Role:** Business analyst

## **Responsibility:**

Deploy payroll system for Vietnam Electricity Corporation (EVN) with more than 200 units:

- Communicate, collect and analyze requirements from clients in calculating payroll business
- Contributing to design UI and database of application
- Writing user guide, SRS document, test case and manage the testing proces

# **BANKING ACADEMY**

Aug 2016 – Apr 2020

- Design and code an application for administrating at Wefly central and ThanhBang milk shop
- Design administration system and code using framework website "Bác sĩ cộng đồng"